On July 8th, we landed at Pearson International Airport in Mississauga and then drove straight up to Georgian Bay.
Hello everyone, we've made it to Georgian Bay, and now we got to take the boat over, but we're here.
We had a pretty laid-back travel day, but it was really nice to have a little boat ride and be on the water.
The boat ride was about 15 minutes before we arrived to the
cottage.
On July 9th, we woke up to a rainy day, which honestly I don't think any of us minded.
It was peaceful, beautiful, relaxing, and that also meant I didn't really feel guilty staying inside when I had a bit of work to do.
Today I've honestly just been doing work.
I have a video to edit, and so I've been working on that.
I'm editing my Peru vlog, and also today has just been kind of raining, so just been staying inside, not doing too much
cottage vibe things.
I wanted to start reading today, but duty calls sometimes, so I have been on my grind with editing.
I'm finding it very difficult to pick out music, but I think I need to take a little bit of a break right now, and I really want
to go for a swim because I haven't swam yet.
And even though it rained all day, the lake is actually still really warm.
So I'm gonna put my bathing suit on and go for the first swim of my time here.
Very excited.
So I'm gonna do that.
Maybe I'll wear my little bathing suit.
This little red one.
It's from Zuko Swim.
It's one of my favorite bathing suits.
I'm gonna put this on and go for a swim.
It's literally such a cute bathing suit.
Okay, let's go for a swim.
It's black fly season, so they're swarming my head.
We got a sunny day today.
It's genuinely so beautiful.
I'm so excited.
Time to beach.
But first, I gotta put on some sunscreen.
'Cause the is like 7 right now.
I using the Illumia Sheer Hydration Broad Spectrum SPF 40.
I gonna go down to the lake.
It like 4.
It like 12:30 right now.
Had
a nice little sesh at the lake.
My hair looks kind of crazy right now, but read my book for a little while.
I'm still reading Our Perfect Storm by Carly Fortune.
I think I have like 100 pages left.
I've been reading this for a long time, but it's been good thus far.
I think her other books I liked more.
I think I liked Every Year After and One Golden Summer better.
So yeah, I don't know.
This one's good, but preferred the other ones, honestly, but I have two more books that I can read after this.
Go on a little paddle.
We got the canoes and the kayaks and everything.
It's gonna be lovely.
Maggie and I are on the kayaks.
Mother and father are in the canoe.
Oh, you know, just out on the lake.
We're going to McCrae Lake, and I think that there are little cliff jumping spots, which is so fun.
Very excited.
Thank
you.
It's
currently like 11.
I'm gonna try and go to sleep now.
I haven't really been able to sleep early the past few nights, but I'm very tired tonight, and I think I'm gonna have a good
sleep, so see y'all tomorrow morning.
Time to go for a boat ride.
On July 11th, we decided to do a little boat day, so we went for a boat ride in search of a perfect spot to have some lunch.
We packed stuff for sandwiches and everything, and eventually found this beautiful little island which was a part of the national park.
So we just hung out there for a little while, had some lunch, and enjoyed the beautiful scenery.
Once we got back to the cottage, we tried to solve some
puzzles, had some dinner, and then played a game before heading to bed.
I'm going to do a little open water swim this morning.
I got my Garmin.
Yeah.
I need to get some exercise, so we're going to go do that.
It was honestly so nice to get out and go for a swim.
I haven't done a lot of swimming recently, and being able to go out and do a open water swim in a warm lake was such a lovely
gift.
I love swimming.
I love being outside, and so what better to do than a nice little swim out there.
Today has been a hella beach day, hella lake day.
It's been really nice, but I actually just finished Our Perfect Storm.
Here's my review.
Um, I would say it's like a 7.
Out of 10, it was a good book.
I didn't really fully get into it just because, like, you kind of know what's going to happen the entire time, and I kind of wish that she
went more into depth with the relationship between Francesca and her mom because I thought that that was really interesting.
But it was a good book, and yeah, good little beach read.
But I feel like I didn't like the characters in this one as much.
Like, I wasn't like as invested in them, so I don't know.
Also, it was like a little bit predictable, but again, still like a very good beach read, I feel.
And then my next book is, I also brought Atmosphere, which I've already started reading, and then Barbarian Days.
But I took this out of the library, and I have to return it in a couple days, so I might just try and read this one
because, because this is my mom's book, so I don't have to return it, but this one I do have to return, so I'm
like, maybe I'll try and finish this.
Okay, so tonight Maggie and I are on dinner,
and we're making, we did this last year, but we're doing like shrimp tacos because they're quick but also very tasty.
This is honestly one of my favorite summer meals.
It literally a coleslaw, a mango salsa, and we made a few sauces as well, and then you just barbecue the shrimp, and it literally takes like less
than an hour to make all this.
It really delicious and very fresh.
After dinner, we had to drop off my cousin and her fiance because they had to go home and head back to work, but my
aunt, my dad, my sister, and I went to go get some ice cream.
We took the boat back and then admired the sunset.
Good morning!
Going
for another little
open swim.
Okay, I started filming.
Okay, synchronized dive.
Yeah, three, two, one.
My goggles came off.
We got some beautiful lunch.
We got burrata, some leftover broccoli salad, some meat, and some chicken.
It is our last day in Ontario, and now we have to
pack up and everything because, well, I guess it's not our last day, I guess we're going home today unfortunately, but it's been such a lovely and relaxing
week.
Just kind of spending all day outside is literally my favourite thing to do, and it's been very nice.
Last swim of our time in the cottage.
Shortly after my swim, we went in and had some lunch, packed everything up, and then headed back to Vancouver.
I'm really grateful that I got to go and spend some time with my family in such a beautiful place.
On to the next adventure.
Thank you all for watching, and hope to see you in the next video.
You.